<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entries on The ENUSAGE Project</title>
    <link>https://enusage.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entries on The ENUSAGE Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://enusage.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>More and More</title>
      <link>https://enusage.github.io/post/more-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://enusage.github.io/post/more-and-more/</guid>
      <description>a growing/increasing number of a mushrooming number of a surging number of increasingly (many) in mounting numbers growingly progressively a flooding tide wax  Examples:
 The Afghan authorities say the airport had been closed for more than a year. The exhibition at Boston&amp;rsquo;s Museum of Fine Arts is more a production than it is a museum display.  More at: https://www.powerthesaurus.org/more_and_more/synonyms</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summarising Research Findings</title>
      <link>https://enusage.github.io/post/summarising-research-findings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://enusage.github.io/post/summarising-research-findings/</guid>
      <description>This study has identified … This study has shown that &amp;hellip; The research has also shown that &amp;hellip; The second major finding was that &amp;hellip; These experiments confirmed that … X made no significant difference to … This study has found that generally &amp;hellip; The investigation of X has shown that &amp;hellip; The results of this investigation show that &amp;hellip; X, Y and Z emerged as reliable predictors of &amp;hellip; Multiple regression analysis revealed that the &amp;hellip; The most obvious finding to emerge from this study is that &amp;hellip; The relevance of X is clearly supported by the current findings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transitional Words: What&#39;s more, Also, Then, Finally ...</title>
      <link>https://enusage.github.io/post/sequencers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://enusage.github.io/post/sequencers/</guid>
      <description>Illustration Thus, for example, for instance, namely, to illustrate, in other words, in particular, specifically, such as.
Contrast On the contrary, contrarily, notwithstanding, but, however, nevertheless, in spite of, in contrast, yet, on one hand, on the other hand, rather, or, nor, conversely, at the same time, while this may be true.
Addition And, in addition to, furthermore, moreover, besides, than, too, also, both-and, another, equally important, first, second, etc., again, further, last, finally, not only-but also, as well as, in the second place, next, likewise, similarly, in fact, as a result, consequently, in the same way, for example, for instance, however, thus, therefore, otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trivially</title>
      <link>https://enusage.github.io/post/trivially/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://enusage.github.io/post/trivially/</guid>
      <description>Obviously
  Clearly
  Anyone can see that
  Trivially
  Indubitably
  It follows that
  Evidently
  By basic applications of previously proven lemmas,
  The proof is left to the reader that
  It goes without saying that
  Consequently
  By immediate consequence,
  Of course
  But then again
  By symmetry</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
